Hello friends, welcome to your company. It
works and is a
leading company in its sector and if seen, it is a
private sector
general insurance company of India which is a private
sector company and if seen, the
company offers a well diversified range of
product and risk management solution
through multiple distribution channels, that is, there are
many different types of
insurance which can be
insurance of any value
like insurance of any vehicle or related to any risk
management
and if seen, there are
multiple channels of insurance within the company's insurance
such as including
motor health distribution channel
including motor fire personal accident
marine engineering and liability
insurance and if seen its segments, then
its segments are fire marine health
including personal accident millions, that is, the
company does all types of
insurance whether it is
health insurance or someone's
life insurance and for any
business like if someone is doing business then it is
related to his business
This company does all types of insurance related to motor vehicles and if the
market cap of the company is seen then the
market cap of the company is 9454 crores and the
stock price of the company is 42.5
and if compared with the industry price then the
industry price is 57.3 and
according to the price, the price of the company has
come to a very reasonable state, that is, the
value of the stock is very reasonable and if the
return on capital employed is seen then
its return on capital is 22.5 and if we
look at the earning burden of the stock then it is 45.1
and the promoters have
517.7 per cent holding in it,
if we look at the current price of the stock then
its current price is 19, sorry 1910,
if we look at the 52 week low and high then the
52 week high is 2302 and
its 52 week low is 1336 and the company has
absolutely  There is no debt and neither is there
any pledge percentage,
which means that the fundamentals of the company are very
good and the company is growing very well,
so friends, if you
see, the company's quarter two
numbers have also come and if you see,
we see that sales are increasing quarter on quarter,
if we look at last year
's, sorry, last quarter, then
we see an increase in sales in this quarter as compared to the previous quarter
and if we talk about expenses,
we are also seeing expenses increasing
and if we talk about net profit,
we see net profit also
increasing quarter on quarter
and the earnings per share has also increased
in this quarter in comparison to the previous quarter,
in the last quarter the
earnings per share was
11.7 which has increased to 14.03 in this quarter,
that the company has presented
very good numbers in this quarter
and if you
look at the promoters' chart, then in this, there is sorry share  If we
look at the holder's chart, we see that the promoters'
holding is
slightly decreasing in comparison to the previous quarter
and the FI has
increased its holding in it in comparison to the previous quarter and if we
look at the holding of DI, then DI has
reduced its stake a bit in it and the
government's holding is the same
and the public's
holding is also seen decreasing in
comparison to the previous quarter. So
friends, if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel, then please subscribe to my channel to
know the latest updates related to the share market
and we have
uploaded many more videos of long term ideas on the channel, do watch them too.
So friends, now let's come to the news,
what is the news about the company,
so
friends, the news is that Nirmal Bank has
upgraded the company's targets,
according to them the stock within a one
year can
show a target of 2000 450 and
in one year it can show us the target of stock %
and if
Talking about the previous trading session,
in the previous trading session, we saw the
stock
closing at 19 10.15, which
means that we saw a decline of only 33 in the stock, which means that if we
talk about the previous training session,
we saw a huge decline in the market,
despite that,
we did not see much decline in the stock, the
stock is only
seen consolidating and if we talk about its 52 week
high, then the stock is currently trading 00 below its 52 week high,
so friends, the company had presented
very good numbers in this quarter
and the fundamentals of the company are
also very good and if we look at its valuation, then
it has also come to a very reasonable price
and whoever wants to hold or invest his money in the stock for long
term purpose i.e. for one year, then he
can do it in it and the
stock can give its investors a return of
30% in one year.  Which is what Target can show
Thank you for watching this video and have a
great day Guy